Ajay
[Music]
I myself Shubh, first of all, please ask
you about the market outlook and half of it too Sir, good morning, good morning,
so all the news is
best, President sparing in and
look at the good correction of your two-three days,
after that there is extra oil, but still
try to give me a little ghee
of 50,000 here, Ayush
profit and looked into correction, subscribe
video, subscribe and I am going to a meeting
and if some profit
booking is used because of Bigg Boss
quote number, then I will
give you update, play music of any other call,
so yesterday I cut Bandhan Bank very hard,
5558 60, that 67 science,
book quality profit before the results,
3% will come, it will get you bail,
35 36840 science, click on the office there,
Tata Power has gone down a little,
book profit there, PNB has gone down to 3610,
book profit there and Godrej Properties
1429 Vidya But that I still think
15% of it will go now  If you say so, I have two
daughters 17, if you say so, I have started
tigers from which Singh is also a sale on Thursday
subscribe consumer shares in the profit
1956 flour best result favorites
that Nifty is also coming then Deol is also
rating Gautami again auto component Bal Krishna
industry 1650 take in childhood 1630
stoploss is 1750 tide of 1725 to 1740 and
effect in selling ICICI Lombard
writing as looking very wick and
in insurance two displayed remotely HDFC Life
ICICI Lombard chilli or 1465 to 70
stoploss of 1495 14648 is one while will give
you these finance wonders things perfect
time job screen me subscribe 6
that 1665 till pimpl chhode karke can 16 inch
and owner 1465 1455 click this link to know more